

Narges Farazan

Software Engineer/Producer

I'm a software engineer with 8 years of experience in video game development. I worked with game engines for multiple platforms and used different development tools. Shipped one of the top-grossing games in Iranian local market.

I was the project manager and the team lead in my past roles. I've successfully coordinated with diverse teams including artists and designers.

I'm known to be self-organized and fast learner. I am now eager to leverage my technical and managerial experience in new IT domains.

Work Experiences

Software Engineer, Producer Massive Miniteam, Pulheim - Germany
Nov 2021 — Present

- Shipped 3+ video games on different platforms (PS4, PS5, Xbox One, Xbox Series, Switch, Stadia).
- Optimized game performance and reduced loading times on games built with Unity Engine.
- Led the porting team as the producer, ensuring smooth communication between teams.
- Developed an in-house time-tracking web app using C# Blazer and Entity Frameworks.
- Built a custom Unreal Engine tool for importing animation assets.
- Automated achievements localization conversion with Excel-toplatform format tools.

Unity Game Programmer, Project Manager/Co-Founder Acid Green Games, Tehran - Iran

Aug 2016 — 2021

- Shipped one of the top-grossing mobile games in the Iranian local market.
- Worked with different backend server providers in JavaScript and C#.
- Designed and implemented MongoDB and SQL databases for our game.
- Led A/B testing to optimize in-game revenue models.
- Managed a cross-functional 8-member team, overseeing communication between marketing, design, and development teams, organizing daily standups, and onboarding new team members.

Video Game Development Teacher, Farzanegan 1 Highschool, Tehran - Iran

Aug 2019 — Aug 2020

 Taught video game development basics with Unity to 10th-grade students at special talents Farzanegan 1 high school.

Info

Address

Köln, Germany

Phone

+49 177 870 3992

Email

nargesfarazan@gmail.com

Date of Birth

22/05/1996

Nationality

Iranian

Technical Skills

- C#
- SQL
- HTML CSS
- Javascript
- Basic Java and Android
- Basic backend development
- Project Management

Software Skills

- Unity Engine
- Visual Studio
- Adobe Photoshop
- Git

Languages

- English (Professional)
- German (Elementary)
- Persian (Native)

Links

<u>Lin</u>kedin

Github: Narges7596

Education and Courses

Bachelor of Computer Software Engineering, Dr. Shariati Vocational and Technical Girls College, Tehran - Iran
Sep 2014 — Aug 2018

Game Development and Programming,
Iran Game Development Institute, Tehran - Iran
2015 — 2016

Projects

Daberna Online (Bingo Bean), Acid Green Games, Programmer/Game Producer
May 2017 — Present

- A Bingo mobile game for Android and iOS.
- Still live and running
- One of the top-grossing games in Iranian local markets.
- Secured an investment from Avagames accelerator for the team.
- I worked on both the client-side (Unity) and the server-side.
- I managed the team to prepare updates and run A/B tests.
- Gained experience in publishing, marketing and user acquisition, data analysis, and user support.

Bingo Bean on Google Play Store

Live TV Tycoon, Acid Green Games, Programmer

Jun 2016 — Mar 2018

- An Idle-tycoon mobile game for Android and iOS, providing the experience of managing a TV station.
- Our team's first commercial experience.
- I worked on all client-side aspects of the project in Unity Live TV Tycoon Website

LIVE IV TYCOOTI WEB

Coin Chef,

Acid Green Games, Game Producer

Feb 2021 — Present

- A coin dozer mobile game for Android with a cooking theme.
- I was the game producer and helped with the programming.

Chicken Police - Paint it RED! Massive Miniteam, Programmer

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Worked on PS5 haptic designs for the cinematic cutscenes

De-Exit,

Massive Miniteam, Programmer

Aug 2022 - Mar 2023

 Worked on performance and memory optimization for porting to consoles (PS4, PS5, Xbox One, Xbox Series)

Honors and Awards

Accepted as 2018 IGDAF Women in Games Ambassadors, IGDA Foundation 2018

Best Game Selected by the Players,

Iran Web and Mobile Festival 2017

For "Daberna Online"

Best Mobile Game Nominee,

Tehran Game Convention 2017

For "Live TV Tycoon"

Most Innovative Mobile Game,

Tehran Game Convention 2017

For "Live TV Tycoon"

First Place,

Fanafzar LevelUp Competition 2016

For "Live TV Tycoon"

Hobbies

- Video Games
- Board Games
- Movies/Series
- Anime
- Hand Crafting

Projects

Airhead,

Massive Miniteam, Programmer

Mar 2023 - Apr 2024

 Debugged and finalized the project for submission on PC and consoles (PS4, PS5, Xbox One, Xbox Series, Switch).

Lethal Honor,

Feb 2017

Massive Miniteam, programmer/producer

Mar 2024 – Present

- Worked on porting the project to consoles and helping polish the game.
- Responsible for the porting production side.

Majestic Life, University Project, Programmer and Designer

• An Android application which gamifies productivity.